### Tina Nenshi Gada

UI / UX Designer | Interaction Designer

Portfolio: http://tinagada.design Contact: 315-806-9787 Email: tgada@oswego.edu

Summary: I am Ui/Ux designer with 4 years of experience working with different industry and application. Coming from a background in both engineering and design, I love connecting the dots between business goals, technical constraints and user satisfaction.

#### **EDUCATION**

Masters in Human Computer Interaction SUNY Oswego University - Graduating in May 2020

Bachelors in Information Technology Mumbai University - June 12 - May 15

#### **SKILLS**

#### Design

Paper sketching, Digital Drawings, Affinity Mapping, Animation, Usability Testing, Wireframing, Storyboarding, Visioning, User flows, Responsive Designs, Heuristic Evaluation, Contextual Inquiry, User survey, Branding, Color theory, typography, motion graphics, 3D, Web design

#### **UX Tools**

Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe XD, Balsamiq, AxureRP, Invision, Sketch, Marvel Studio, After Effects, Procreate, Keynote, Principle, Adobe Creative Suite, Adobe CC, Qualtrics

#### **Technical**

HTML5, CSS3, JS, SQL, React JS, Tomcat, Apache, Wordpress, Bootstrap

#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

#### **UI DESIGN FOR FINDING FIVE**

Worked as Lead UX Designer for the finding five startup company for building the application for research study market place.

#### **CAN WIC 2019**

Presented a research paper on the health care application "We Care".

Received certificate for participation and fund for further research.

# WINNER - WOMEN IN COMPUTING HACKATHON

Best UI Designs and Wireframing of Application for Food Rescue Application at New York, 2018

### **SUNY OSWEGO DEAN AWARD**

Full-time tuition waiver as Graduate Student for Fall 2018

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# User Experience Designer Intern at SUNY CPD, Syracuse, NY (Aug 2019 - Present)

- Pitched the ability to filter and sort courses in by additional parameters after validating user needs & designing the mock-up for SUNY CPD website; expected to go live in Q1 2020 and increase user-conversion rate.
- Conducted user research, design sketches and prototyped the SUNY CPD website based on the feedback which helped improve performance and number of visits by 4.5%.
- Complying the WCAG 2.0 accessibility guidelines and considering the user feedback after usability testing.
- Reported visual design inconsistencies based on heuristic evaluation and proposed prioritization criteria to fix those inconsistencies; 3 out of 30 proposals already live on website.
- Worked in collaboration with event manager and other team members to design brochures, flyers, posters for different conferences by considering brand guidelines.
- Updated the visual style guide to unify the branding language, improving productivity of UX designers by ~4.4%.

## User Experience Designer Intern at OTO Capital, Mumbai, IN (May 2019 - Aug 2019)

- Designed the responsive interface for their mobile application and web console using Adobe XD.
- Created and conducted an A/B test to evaluate a new interface using UX metrics. New designs increased the user experience by 15%.
- Analysed and synthesized research findings into new design ideas, created wireframes, and high-fidelity prototypes using Adobe XD.
- Collaborated with product managers, developers, and marketers to enhance the and polish the product features and meet business goals.
- · Deliver the product from ideation to final delivery till launch.

# Graduate Research Assistant at SUNY Oswego, Oswego, NY (Aug 2018 - May 2019)

- Reviewed the research studies, worked on hypotheses and re-run the experiment with the new bunch of the participants to verify the results of the studies.
- Instructed 100+ participants from diverse backgrounds by clarifying experiment procedures independently.

## Ui/Ux Developer at Seclore Pvt. Ltd, Mumbai, IN (Oct 2015 - July 2018)

- Improved product UI by reducing the drop offs and enabling faster access to IRM
  protected documents for authorized users by streamlining new user onboarding,
  authentication, file access request and approval flows.
- Designed user journeys, wireframes, and interfaces for new features for the mobile application.
- Implemented single sign-on, user account management, build a web application, designed its UI and developed the site as a full stack web developer to make interaction easier.
- Design user interface with motion graphics and animations for the secure application.
- Conducted and drove accessibility testing with other UI Team members on designs before it shared with developers.
- · Developed responsive products using HTML, CSS & JavaScript.